it's a bit better because sneak had no
vowels so at least we've gone from this
is the zero to one it's it's an
evolution it's progress right every
every company you get a little bit
better yeah so Tesla is the new company
that I founded earlier this year it
indeed focuses pris on AI native sofware
development our goal and I say our here
because Simon you're helping build this
Dev movement here and this motion and
change alongside the company our goal
really is on one hand as we're doing
here in this podcast is help promote
this idea of AI native software
development help shape this with the
community help prepare us all into this
next generation of software development
and build a platform that enables that
build a platform that is a sort of built
for AI native software development
across its life cycle there's a lot of
unknowns over there we're still figuring
it out as we're doing it uh and that's
the fun in it